export const quizData =  {
    "quizTitle": "React Quiz Component Demo",
    "quizSynopsis": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim",
    "nrOfQuestions": "4",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "How can you access the state of a component from inside of a member function?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "questionPic": "https://dummyimage.com/600x400/000/fff&text=X", // if you need to display Picture in Question
        "answerSelectionType": "single",
        "answers": [
          "this.getState()",
          "this.prototype.stateValue",
          "this.state",
          "this.values"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
        "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
        "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
        "point": "20"
      },
      {
        "question": "ReactJS is developed by _____?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerSelectionType": "single",
        "answers": [
          "Google Engineers",
          "Facebook Engineers"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2",
        "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
        "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
        "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
        "point": "20"
      },
      {
        "question": "ReactJS is an MVC based framework?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerSelectionType": "single",
        "answers": [
          "True",
          "False"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2",
        "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
        "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
        "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
        "point": "10"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following concepts is/are key to ReactJS?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerSelectionType": "single",
        "answers": [
          "Component-oriented design",
          "Event delegation model",
          "Both of the above",
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
        "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
        "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
        "point": "30"
      },
      {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit,",
        "questionType": "photo",
        "answerSelectionType": "single",
        "answers": [
          "https://dummyimage.com/600x400/000/fff&text=A",
          "https://dummyimage.com/600x400/000/fff&text=B",
          "https://dummyimage.com/600x400/000/fff&text=C",
          "https://dummyimage.com/600x400/000/fff&text=D"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1",
        "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
        "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
        "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
        "point": "20"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the advantages of React JS?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerSelectionType": "multiple",
        "answers": [
          "React can be used on client and as well as server side too",
          "Using React increases readability and makes maintainability easier. Component, Data patterns improves readability and thus makes it easier for manitaining larger apps",
          "React components have lifecycle events that fall into State/Property Updates",
          "React can be used with any other framework (Backbone.js, Angular.js) as it is only a view layer"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": [1, 2, 4],
        "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
        "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
        "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
        "point": "20"
      },
    ]
  } 

// [
//   {
//       "question": "What is the purpose of the flattened layer in a neural network?",
//       "options": [
//           {"a": "To convert the input image into a one-dimensional array"},
//           {"b": "To add more layers to the neural network"},
//           {"c": "To optimize the loss function"}
//       ],
//       "answer": "a"
//   },
//   {
//       "question": "What is the activation function used in the dense layer with 128 neurons?",
//       "options": [
//           {"a": "Sigmoid"},
//           {"b": "Rectified Linear"},
//           {"c": "Tanh"}
//       ],
//       "answer": "b"
//   },
//   {
//       "question": "What is the purpose of the output layer in the neural network for clothing type prediction?",
//       "options": [
//           {"a": "To convert the output into a two-dimensional array"},
//           {"b": "To determine the importance of variables"},
//           {"c": "To predict the likelihood of each clothing type"}
//       ],
//       "answer": "c"
//   }
// ]

// [
//   {
//       "question": "What is the purpose of the flattened layer in building a neural network with TensorFlow?",
//       "options": [
//           {"a": "To convert the input image into a one-dimensional array"},
//           {"b": "To add more layers to the neural network"},
//           {"c": "To optimize the loss function"}
//       ],
//       "answer": "a"
//   },
//   {
//       "question": "What is the activation function used in the dense layer with 128 fully connected neurons?",
//       "options": [
//           {"a": "Sigmoid"},
//           {"b": "Rectified Linear"},
//           {"c": "Tanh"}
//       ],
//       "answer": "b"
//   },
//   {
//       "question": "What is the purpose of the output layer in the neural network for predicting clothing types?",
//       "options": [
//           {"a": "To convert the output into a one-dimensional array"},
//           {"b": "To determine the importance of a given variable"},
//           {"c": "To predict the likelihood of an image being a certain type of clothing"}
//       ],
//       "answer": "c"
//   }
// ]